(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Fleur
作詞: Neko Hacker 作曲: 山田 高弘
Lyrics: Neko Hacker / Composition: Takahiro Yamada
雪が降り この夜を
Snow is falling, and this night...
月明かりが 照らしてく
...is being lit up by the moonlight.
好きなフリ とかじゃない
It's not just like I'm pretending to like you.
本当の気持ちに
I've finally realized...
初めて気がついた
...my true feelings for the first time.
始まりは いつだって
The beginning is always...
突然の ストーリー
...a sudden story.
君のことを 考えるだけで
Just by thinking about you,
想い 溢れてく
My feelings overflow.
雪が煌めく この花束
This bouquet of sparkling snow,
抱えて祈ってる
I hold it and pray,
君に渡せるように
So that I can give it to you.
指先が 震える まだかな
My fingertips are trembling, is it time yet?
待ってるね いつだって
I'm waiting, always,
この想い
For these feelings...
届けを
...to reach you.
意味もなく 過ごしてた
I was spending my days without meaning,
日々を変えてくれたから
But you changed those days for me.
一言くらいあるよねってそっと
"At least say something," I thought as I softly...
寄り添ってあげたいな
...wanted to stay close to you.
終わらないでと願う 大切なモーメント
Wishing it would never end, this precious moment.
知りたくても知りたくはないの ここに閉じ込めて
Even if I want to know, I don't want to know. Lock it away here.
たった一つだけのわがまま 叶えてくれるかな
Will you grant me my only selfish wish?
一番にしてよね
Make me your number one.
運命と言うには まだまだ足りない
To call it destiny, it's still not enough.
でもずっと君だけを
But I'll always only be...
見てるよ
...looking at you.
雪が煌めくこの花束
This bouquet where the snow sparkles...
抱えて祈ってる 君に渡せるように
...I hold it and pray, so that I can give it to you.
指先が震える まだかな
My fingertips are trembling. Is it time yet?
待ってるね
I'll be waiting.
いつだってこの思い
Always, this feeling...
届けよ
...reach you!
好きだよ
I love you.
ほら行こうぜ そうだみんな行こうぜ
Hey, let's go! That's right, everyone let's go!
さあほら歌おうぜ そうだみんな歌おうぜ
Come on, let's sing! That's right, everyone let's sing!
ほら誓おうぜ そうだみんな誓おうぜ
Hey, let's make a vow! That's right, everyone let's make a vow!
さあほら愛そうぜ 最高級で愛そうぜ
Come on, let's love! Let's love with the highest quality!
ザ☆ピ〜ス！
The☆Peace!
ほら行こうぜ Everybody Get Up!
Hey, let's go! Everybody Get Up!
うちらが住む未来だぜ Let's Get Up! Get Up!
It's the future we live in! Let's Get Up! Get Up!
Everybody Peace! 意味ないけどコンビニが好き
Everybody Peace! For no reason, I like convenience stores!
Ha Ha Ha Ha...
ピザポテトだぜ ふるさとには さら一週間帰ろう
Pizza potato! Let's go back to our hometown for another week.
英会話スクール 肺活量 行けてないぜ
English conversation school, lung capacity, I haven't gone!
Ha Ha Ha Ha...
ほら行こうぜ Peace Peace!
Hey, let's go! Peace Peace!
選挙の日って ウチらまじか
Election day... are we serious?
投票行って 外食するんだ
Go to vote, and then eat out.
ワンダフル 素敵な未来 描くなくらい 凄いデンジャラス Let's Go!
Wonderful! Drawing a lovely future... so dangerous! Let's Go!
好きな人が優しかった
The person I like was kind.
嬉しい出来事が増えました
Happy events have increased.
大事な人がわかってくれた
The person important to me understood.
感動的な出来事となりました
It became a moving event.
Wow Wow Wow Wow Peace Peace!
ほら行こうぜ Everybody Peace!
Hey, let's go! Everybody Peace!
いつも悩む AかBか Peace Peace!
Always worrying, A or B? Peace Peace!
盛り上がり どこでもいいわ
Getting excited... anywhere is fine.
…は 君にいくね
...is going to you
ハハハハハ
Hahahahaha
ほら行こうぜ！ ピース！ピース！
Come on, let's go! Peace! Peace!
達成感遂げちゃ
Once you've achieved success,
決めらんないのは
what you can't decide on
恋愛のエトセトラ
is the etcetera of romance
いっせーの！レッツゴー！レッツゴー！
One, two, go! Let's go! Let's go!
道行く人が親切だった (ピース！)
The people on the street were kind (Peace!)
嬉しい出来事がありました (Yeah! ピース！)
Something happy happened (Yeah! Peace!)
愛おしい人が正直でした (ピース！)
My beloved person was honest (Peace!)
全てを受け止めようと感じました (Yeah!)
I felt like I should accept everything (Yeah!)
Wow wow wow wow Peace! Wow wow...
青春の1ページって 地球の歴史からするとどれくらいなんだろう？
How long is one page of youth in the history of the Earth?
ああ 愛おしいあの人 お昼ご飯何食べたんだろう？
Ah, my beloved... I wonder what they had for lunch?
ほら行こうぜ！ そうだ皆行こうぜ！
Come on, let's go! That's right, everyone let's go!
さあほら歌おうぜ！ そうだ皆歌おうぜ！
Come on, let's sing! That's right, everyone let's sing!
ほら誓おうぜ！ そうだ皆誓おうぜ！
Come on, let's vow! That's right, everyone let's vow!
さあほら愛そうぜ！ 最高級で愛そうぜ！
Come on, let's love! Let's love in the highest class!
Wow... (ピース！ピース！)
Wow... (Peace! Peace!)
道行く人が正直だった (ピース！)
The people on the street were honest (Peace!)
嬉しい出来事がありました (Yeah! ピース！)
Something happy happened (Yeah! Peace!)
愛おしい人が正直でした (Yeah! ピース！)
My beloved person was honest (Yeah! Peace!)
全てを受け止めようと感じました (Yeah!)
I felt like I should accept everything (Yeah!)
ラミィ！ お誕生日おめでとうー！
Lamy! Happy Birthday!
ラミィ！ お誕生日おめでと～！！
Lamy! Happy Birthday!!
何だこれ何だこれ。凄い絵面。
What's this? What's this? What a sight.
飲むの？とりあえず乾杯しよう。
Are we drinking? Let's have a toast for now.
こちらはノエルのポーションでございやす。
This here is Noel's potion.
ノエポ。では皆さん一緒に飲みましょう。
NoePo. Now then, let's all drink together.
かんぱーい！
Cheers!
どうした？
What's wrong?
旨！めっちゃ爽やかな味だよ。
Tasty! It's such a refreshing taste.
犬には早かったか？ｗ
Was it too early for a dog? lol
ジンだからね。色んなボタニカルが。
It's Gin, you see. Lots of botanicals.
自然なナチュラルな感じの気がしてね。
It has a natural feel to it.
上にハッシュタグ的なものが。すごいじゃん。
There's like a hashtag thing at the top. Amazing.
台本どんどん飛ばしてくね。
You're skipping the script like crazy.
「いやぁ良いんですか？ ラミィの誕生日でゲストに呼んで頂いたんですけど、こんな寛いじゃって。」
'Well, is it okay? I was invited as a guest for Lamy's birthday, but making myself so at home.'
「良いんですよ～！」
'It's okay~!'
ラミィちゃんのセリフだったこれ。
That was Lamy-chan's line.
グダグダや、ごめん。
It's a mess, sorry.
今日はね、かねてから登録者数100万人達成したら
Today, as I decided long ago, once I reach 1 million subscribers
100万円分のお酒を飲むと決めてたのにね、飲んじゃおうと思います！
I'd drink 1 million yen worth of alcohol, and now I'm going to do it!
ということで、本日のハッシュタグがこちら！
So, here is today's hashtag!
#やかまし100万円飲み会！いえーい！
#Noisy1MillionYenDrinkingParty! Yay!
100万円分飲めるってことですね？
So you mean we can drink 1 million yen worth?
今日はお酒が前半戦で…
Today, Japanese sake is for the first half...
日本酒が前半戦で...
Sake is for the first half...
ええ。
Yeah.
後半戦が、えーと、ワインを用意しております。
And for the second half, well, we have wine ready.
おお〜！ワイン！
Ohh! Wine!
ということで、まず日本酒ということなんですけれども...
So, we're starting off with the sake section, but...
日本酒といえば!?
Speaking of sake!?
ここで...
At this point...
ゲストを用意しております！
We have a guest ready!
日本酒といえば、日本酒といえば！
Speaking of sake, speaking of sake!
こんこよ〜！こんこよ〜！
Konkoyo! Konkoyo!
※博衣こより
*Hakui Koyori
ハローハロー！
Hello, hello!
おめでとうございま〜す！
Congratulations!
日本酒 飲めるんすかぁ〜！？
Can you drink sake!?
日本酒飲めますよ、100万円分のね！！
I can drink sake, especially 1 million yen worth!
ちょっとね、面白い日本酒を色々用意したんで...
I've prepared several interesting sakes...
紹介していきたいと思います！はい！
So I'd like to introduce them! Yes!
えーちゃん、よろしくお願いします！！
A-chan, please take it away!
はい、商品の紹介は私、ホロライブスタッフ友人Aが行います。
Yes, I, Hololive staff member Friend A, will introduce the items.
やかまし100万円飲み会、最初のお酒は『零響 -Absolute 0-』。
For the Noisy 1 Million Yen Drinking Party, the first sake is 'Reikyo -Absolute 0-'.
精米歩合50%以下の日本酒は何という？
Do you know what sake with a rice polishing ratio of 50% or less is called?
え、何て呼ばれるんですか？
Eh, what is it called?
大、大、大吟醸！あ、大吟醸！
Da-, Da-, Daiginjo! Ah, Daiginjo!
聞いたことある〜！
I've heard of that!
大吟醸＝高級酒に位置づけられるんですよ。
It's classified as Daiginjo, a high-end sake.
なんとこの『零響』、精米歩合が0.85%。
Amazingly, this 'Reikyo' has a rice polishing ratio of 0.85%.
え〜！ほぼ、ほぼない！！
Eh! Almost, almost nothing left!!
お米全体の99.15%を削って、残り0.85%のみを使用して造られたお酒。
It's sake brewed using only the remaining 0.85% after polishing away 99.15% of the rice grain.
もうキンキンに研ぎ澄まされた部分だけで...
Only using the most intensely refined part...
スゲー！
Amazing!
お米の真ん中の真ん中の真ん中の真ん中だけなの！
It's just the very, very, very center of the rice!
見えな〜い！
I can't see it!
なんとあの、5297時間、221日もの時間をかけて精米。
It took 5,297 hours, or 221 days, just for the polishing process.
じっくりとお米を磨くそうですよ。
They polish the rice very slowly and carefully.
詳しいなこいつ。
He's quite knowledgeable.
匠の技ですね。
It's a master's craft.
メガネかけてそうだもんな。
Sounds like someone who wears glasses.
お値段こちら...
The price is...
38万5000円！ええええ〜！？高い！
385,000 yen! Eeeee!? So expensive!
大事に、大事にお楽しみください。
Please enjoy it very, very carefully.
これね、38万5000円...
This one, 385,000 yen...
一年分の食費くらいじゃないですか！？
Isn't that like a year's worth of food expenses!?
一年...？絶妙だよな。
A year...? That's a specific amount.
みんな、かんぱーい！！
Everyone, cheers!!
38万5000円、お楽しみください。
Please enjoy the 385,000 yen.
あ、なんかすごい！匂いがすご〜い！
Ah, wow! The smell is amazing!
ラミィ これどんな匂いですか？
Lamy, what kind of smell is this?
これはですね、もう削りに削り取られた、もう雑味のないッ！！
This is, well, it's been polished and polished, so there's absolutely no bitterness!!
顔隠れてますよ？
Your face is hidden, you know?
旨味しかない吟醸香！！
A Ginjo aroma that's pure umami!!
みんな生きてるうちに、もう嗅ぐことないこれ、本当に！
You'll never smell this again in your lifetime, seriously!
すごーい！
Amazing!
飲みやすい！飲みやすい！
So easy to drink! So easy to drink!
え、飲んだの！？飲んだの！？
Eh, you drank it!? You already drank it!?
フライング？飲んだw
A false start? She drank it lol.
うまッ！！うまッ！！
Good!! It's good!!
あ、なんか... 飲みやすい！
Ah, wow... It's so easy to drink!
「匂い的に無理かもしれん...」って思ったけど、美味いわ...
I thought 'I might not handle the smell...', but it's delicious...
雑味のない！この精米歩合0.85%！！
No bitterness! This 0.85% rice polishing ratio!!
雑味はなくてスッキリとした、でも飲みやすいの。これは素晴らしい一品ですよ。
It's clear without bitterness, yet easy to drink. This is a wonderful item.
な〜んか みんな足りなくないですか？
Doesn't everyone feel like we're missing something?
はい！おなか空いたなぁ〜
Yes! I'm hungry!
おなか空いたぁ〜！何か食べたいな〜！
I'm hungry! I want to eat something!
おつまみも力を入れております！！
We've also put a lot of effort into the snacks!!
おつまみも！入ってるんですか！？
Snacks too! Are they included!?
えーちゃん 紹介よろしくお願いします！！
A-chan, please introduce them!
お待たせしました、最初のおつまみは『からすみ』。
Thanks for waiting, the first snack is 'Karasumi' (mullet roe).
皆さんは、からすみの原料って知ってますか？
Do you all know what the ingredient for Karasumi is?
からすみってさ、食べたことないんだけど、これって正体なに？
I've never eaten Karasumi, but what exactly is it?
スミじゃないの？イカスミじゃないの？
Isn't it ink? Like squid ink?
イカスミではない。
It's not squid ink.
卵巣ですよね？
It's the ovary, right?
誰の卵？カラスの？
Whose eggs? A crow's?
カラス！？鳥になっちゃったw
A crow!? Now it's a bird lol.
ボラの卵巣となっております。
It is actually the ovary of a mullet fish.
ボラって何よ？お魚じゃない？
What's a mullet? Isn't it a fish?
ボラ... え、こんなの腹ん中に入ってんの！？
A mullet... wait, this is inside its belly!?
そう、それをギュッとしてるんじゃない？
Yeah, and it's probably compressed like that.
タラコとかと同じってことですよね。
So it's the same idea as Tarako (cod roe).
はい、そしてもう一つ行きますか！
Yes, and shall we go with one more!
まだあるんだ。
There's more.
もう一つなんだ？
Wait, there's another one?
口に入れた瞬間、とろける幸せ。
Happiness that melts the moment you put it in your mouth.
続いては、海の幸から一級品のウニです。
Next, a top-quality sea urchin from the sea.
テッカテカだぁ〜！
It's so shiny!
ヤバッ！美味しそう！
Whoa! Looks delicious!
うわぁ、いい色ですね。
Wow, what a beautiful color.
すげぇ、食べたい！
Amazing, I want to eat it!
ラミィたん、先に食べな〜。
Lamy-tan, you should eat first.
そうそう。先にお願いします。
Right, right. Please, go ahead.
いいの？
Is it okay?
じゃあちょっと、うにから...
Then, from the sea urchin...
ざばっと取って良い？
Can I take a big scoop?
あ、ごめんね、ちょっと見えないかもしれないけど。
Ah, sorry, you might not be able to see it.
どうですか？食べてみてくださいよ。
How is it? Please, give it a try.
う〜ん！！！
Mmm!!!
どんな味？うに？
How's the taste? Sea urchin?
うにうにうに！うに味！
Uni, uni, uni! It tastes like uni!
濃厚なうにの味。なんかさ、臭みが全然ない！！
A rich sea urchin taste. Like, there's no fishy smell at all!!
それは素晴らしい。さすがでございます。
That's wonderful. As expected.
人生で初めて、からすみ食べてみようかな。
I think I'll try karasumi for the first time in my life.
日本酒に合いますからね。あとでお酒を。
It goes well with sake. Have some sake later.
ぼくはボラ...
I'm a mullet...
ボラになるはずだった...
I was supposed to be a mullet...
そんな言い方したら食べづらいじゃないですか！！
When you put it like that, it makes it hard to eat!!
ぼくはボラ...
I'm a mullet...
あ、でも気にせず食べてます。
Ah, but I'm eating without a care.
さあ、感想はどうでしょうか？
Now, what are your impressions?
なんなんだろう、シャケみたい...
What is this, it's like salmon...
シャケ！？シャケなんだ。
Salmon?! It's salmon.
卵なのに身みたいってこと？
You mean it's like flesh even though it's roe?
逆にみんな、ちょっと食べてみて！
Actually, everyone, give it a try!
いただきまーす！
Let's eat!
はい、どうぞ、どうぞ。
Yes, go ahead, go ahead.
イカスミ...
Squid ink...
イカスミじゃない！イカスミじゃないです！
It's not squid ink! It's not squid ink!
からすみ！
Karasumi!
からすみ、からすみです。
Karasumi, it's karasumi.
どうかな？シャケっぽくない？魚、うん、うん。
How is it? Doesn't it taste like salmon? Fish, yeah, yeah.
なんか止まってますけど大丈夫ですか？w
You've kind of stopped moving, are you okay? lol
え、これを、この高い日本酒でかきこむ、こうやって。
Wait, you wash this down with this expensive sake, like this.
どうですか？合いますか？
How is it? Does it pair well?
濃厚で合う〜！！
It's rich and it pairs so well!!
美味〜い！！
Delicious!!
美味しすぎる。ころねさん！
It's too delicious. Korone-san!
あ、大丈夫です！あはははは！
Ah, I'm okay! Hahahaha!
なんか、誰かに乗り移られたみたいな。
It's like she's been possessed by someone.
でも、これすごい飲みやすいよ！
But, this is really easy to drink!
ころね！？
Korone!?
危ない、危ない。早いよ、早いよ。
Watch out, watch out. You're going too fast, too fast.
まだ始まったばっかだよ。
It's only just started.
コップ半分も飲んでないからね。
You haven't even finished half a glass.
うあそう...
Oh, right...
醤油もいいよ。卵だもんね。
Soy sauce is good too. Since it's roe.
こよりもらいたい。
I want Koyori's.
あ、「こより」じゃねぇや。戌神ころね。
Ah, I'm not "Koyori." I'm Inugami Korone.
自分をこよりだと思い込み始めてしまった。
She's starting to believe she's Koyori.
こよりもらいたい。
I want Koyori's.
大丈夫？w
Are you okay? lol
それ醤油だから！！
That's soy sauce!!
醤油飲まないで！！
Don't drink the soy sauce!!
ここで、もう一本。
Here's another bottle.
約50年もの間、洞窟で眠っていた日本酒。
A sake that has been sleeping in a cave for about 50 years.
当時、鑑評会に出品する最高のお酒を、
At that time, the best sake to be exhibited at the competition...
ビール瓶に詰めて取っていたものだそうですよ。
...was apparently stored in beer bottles.
おぉー、すごい！これ。
Ooh, this is amazing.
歴史ありますね。
It has quite a history.
瓶にビールって書いてあるけど、ビールじゃない！
It says "beer" on the bottle, but it's not beer!
こちらがいくらですか？
How much is this one?
こちらはお値段、
The price for this one is...
30万円です。
...300,000 yen.
えぇー！！これも30万するの！？
Eh!! This one costs 300,000 yen too!?
やばーい！！
No way!!
色が、色がだいぶ違いますね。
The color, the color is quite different.
古酒ですからね。かなり色が...
It's because it's aged sake. The color is quite...
え、これってなんだっけ？
Wait, what was this again?
これなんだっけ？日本酒？
What was it? Sake?
あぁ、日本酒かw 日本酒のコーナーだから。
Ah, sake, right. lol It's the sake corner after all.
色ついてるパターンもありえるのか...
So a colored version is possible too...
古酒は大体、黄色くなりますからね。
Aged sake usually turns yellow, you know.
そうなんだ。有名な話か。
I see. Is that common knowledge?
香りもちょっと、酸っぱ味のある感じ。
The scent also has a bit of an acidic feel.
匂い嗅いでみてください。
Please, try smelling it.
いーー！！！
Eeeh!!!
何？何？その反応は何？
What? What? What's with that reaction?
酸っぱ！！
Sour!!
酸っぱくてびっくりしたのね。びっくりした。
It was so sour it surprised you. Surprised.
バルサミコ酢？
Balsamic vinegar?
なんか訛ってますけど大丈夫ですか？
You're speaking with an accent, are you okay?
バルサミコ酢？
Balsamic vinegar?
いつも以上に訛ってますけどw
You're accent is stronger than usual. lol
かんぱーい！！
Cheers!!
どうですか？お味は。
How is it? The taste.
まぁ、まぁ、ちょっとずつ、ちょっとずつね。
Well, well, little by little, little by little.
はい。味の実況して。どうですか？
Yes. Give us a taste report. How is it?
バルサミコ酢？
Balsamic vinegar?
良いのか？それでw
Is that okay? Saying that? lol
バルサミコ酢？30万ですけど？
Balsamic vinegar? It's 300,000 yen, you know?
え、こよりちゃん、どう？
Wait, Koyori-chan, how is it?
古酒ならではの深い味がするんですけど、
It has that deep flavor unique to aged sake...
後味スッキリしてるから、めちゃめちゃ飲みやすい！
But the aftertaste is so clean, it's incredibly easy to drink!
レポーターや！ソムリエ？
What a reporter! A sommelier?
案件来てる？すごい！
Are you getting sponsorship deals? Amazing!
え、これをさ、飲ませてくれてありがとうね。
Hey, thank you for letting me drink this.
貴重なお酒を。まだ終わりじゃない！まだ終わりじゃない！
Such rare sake. But it's not over yet! Not over yet!
まだあるの！？
There's more!?
まだあるん〜！！まだ前半戦なんだ！！
There's more!! This is still only the first half!!
はい、前半戦か。後半戦もあるんで。
Right, the first half. There's a second half too.
誰もルール聞いてなかったですからね。忘れちゃった。
No one was listening to the rules. I completely forgot.
はい、ここで！
Alright, and now!
宴会にはもってこいの！ゲームを用意してありまーす！
Perfect for a banquet! I've prepared a game!
なんだ？なになに？
What is it? What, what?
王様だーれだ！
Who is the King!
違う、違う。待って、待って。まだ、まだ。
No, no. Wait, wait. Not yet, not yet.
それ違う！
That's not it!
それでは！
And now!
ツイスターゲーム！！イェーイ！！
Twister game!! Yay!!
ツイスターゲームのルールは
The rules for Twister are...
皆さんご存知ということで
...well-known to everyone, so...
最初の対戦カードは、戌神ころね対雪花ラミィ
The first match is Inugami Korone vs Yukihana Lamy.
ルーレットは、私友人Eが務めさせていただきます
I, Friend-chan, will be handling the roulette.
いくぞ！祝われなさいよ！
Let's go! Celebrate me!
今日の主役、頑張ってください
Today's star, please do your best.
左足、緑にお願いします
Left foot on green, please.
下から...良いです...
From below... Okay.
Wow~! 速い！
Wow~! So fast!
張り切っております
She's fired up.
右足、赤で
Right foot on red.
こんな速いの？
She's this fast?
迷いがない
No hesitation.
右手、黄色
Right hand on yellow.
良いじゃないですか
Looking good.
余裕そうですよ？
You look like you have room to spare.
おっ、なんと、ころねさんも右手黄色で
Oh, amazingly, Korone-san's right hand is also yellow.
余裕じゃん、全然
She's totally fine.
今のところ大丈夫そうですね
Everything seems okay so far.
ころねさん、右手、青です
Korone-san, right hand on blue.
なんか落ち着いてるなぁ...
She seems so calm...
あっ！ハプニングマスに止まってしまいました
Ah! You landed on a Happening square.
右手を黄色の円に置いて、ダジャレを言ってください
Put your right hand on yellow and say a pun.
うわぁぁ、そういうのもあるの！？
Whoa, there's even that kind of thing!?
ダジャレ...
A pun...
「あらヨット」さん
"Arayotto!"
今「あらヨット」っつったの誰ですか？
Who just said "Arayotto"?
ヨット...なんだっけ...
Yacht... what was it...
もう忘れちゃったよ...
I've already forgotten it...
ダジャレを言うのは、誰じゃ！？
Who's the one (dare ja) saying a pun!?
すんません！！！
I'm sorry!!!
10秒間大きな声で叫んでください
Please shout loudly for 10 seconds.
お酒びあーーーーー！
SHOUTING FOR ALCOHOL!
左足、緑
Left foot on green.
左足、青
Left foot on blue.
あっ、おちりが！！
Ah, my butt!!
見えた！これは！
I saw it! This is!
覗くな！！
Don't peek!!
ゲロゲ～ロ！
Ribbit, ribbit!
お願い、見ないで！
Please don't look!
記念撮影撮っていいですよ
You can take a commemorative photo.
頑張れ、ラミィ！
Go for it, Lamy!
左手を緑の円に置いて、隣のプレイヤーとじゃんけんをしてください
Put your left hand on green and play rock-paper-scissors with the person next to you.
じゃ～んけ～ん、ぽん！
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
負けたけど？
I lost though?
勝ったけど？
I won though?
終わりですｗ
That's it. lol
特に何かある訳ではない
Nothing in particular happens.
右手を黄色の円に置いて、好きな果物を言ってください
Put your right hand on yellow and say your favorite fruit.
バナナ
Banana.
右手、上げてください
Raise your right hand.
キープで
Keep it there.
二人とも無難な位置に置くからさ
They're both placing them in safe spots.
相手が行けないような位置に
You need to place them where they can't reach.
次、攻撃的に行こう
Let's be aggressive next time.
右手、赤でお願いします
Right hand on red, please.
妨害！！
Interference!!
真剣だ、ほら
Look, they're serious.
右足、赤
Right foot on red.
これもう動けないよ！？
I can't move anymore!?
同じとこには置けません！！
You can't place it in the same spot!!
こっちしかない...
This is the only way...
無理っ！無理ぃ～！！
Impossible! I can't do it!!
これは詰んだのでは？
Is this checkmate?
雪花ラミィ、OUT！
Yukihana Lamy, OUT!
戌神ころね、WIN！
Inugami Korone, WIN!
基礎体力が違いますからね
The basic physical strength is just different.
第2回戦もありますからね！
There's also a second round!
続いては、白銀ノエル、宝鐘マリン
Up next: Shirogane Noel, Houshou Marine,
博衣こよりの三つ巴大乱戦の予感！
and Hakui Koyori. A three-way melee is coming!
左足、黄色
Left foot on yellow.
冷静にね、まずは一歩踏み出して
Stay calm, just take the first step.
仲良しですね
How friendly.
右手、黄色
Right hand on yellow.
早速近い
Getting close already.
ノエルなんか、股が！！
Noel, your legs are!!
気をつけて
Be careful.
まだ何もしてないのに勝手に開き出した
I haven't even done anything, but they opened on their own.
右手、赤。ノエルの邪魔になる場所に
Right hand on red. Place it to block Noel.
ここ。いいいね、いいね
Right here. Good, good.
左手、赤
Left hand on red.
ここかな
Maybe here.
これこれ！！見たかったやつぅ～！！
Yes! This is what I wanted to see!!
その体制キツいだろ
That position must be tough.
大丈夫か？ｗ
Are you okay? lol
右手、緑
Right hand on green.
右足、青
Right foot on blue.
右足、赤でございます
It's right foot on red.
近いですねぇ
You're very close.
知恵の輪みたいになってる
It's like a brain teaser puzzle.
左足、浮かしてください
Lift your left foot.
左足浮かす！？
Lift left foot!?
いつまで！？
Until when!?
ずっとですぅ
Forever.
左手、緑でお願いします
Left hand on green, please.
こよりの手がああ！！
Koyori's hand, ah!!
持ってかれたああ〜！！
Taken away...!!
マリンさん 右足青
Marine-san, right foot blue
左足はどうしたらいいの･･･？
What should I do with my left foot...?
浮かせたままです
Keep it floating
浮かせたまま！？
Keep it floating!?
宝鐘マリン OUT
Houshou Marine OUT
いや無理だろ！！
No way, that's impossible!!
浮かせたままないだろ！！
There's no way I can keep it floating!!
右手赤
Right hand red
ここに行くしかないですね
I have no choice but to go here
絡んでるね〜！！
They're entangled~!!
絡んでる絡んでるぅ
Entangled, entangled
ハプニングマス
Happening square
『耳フゥー』しますかね
Let's do 'Ear blowing', shall we?
来ちゃったあ〜（喜）
It's here~ (joy)
マリン、やったれ！
Marine, go for it!
いくぞぉッ！！
Here I go!!
やめてぃ
Stop it
逃げないで！
Don't run away!
いきま〜す！
Here I go~!
なんだこの絵面
What kind of scene is this?
ヨユ〜ｗ
So calm~ lol
冷たいけど温かい♡
Cold but warm heart
「冷たいけど温かい」ってなにｗ
"Cold but warm", what is that lol
今の気分はどうですか？
How do you feel right now?
気分は最悪です
I feel terrible
こよりは最高でしたよ♪
Koyori felt great♪
いや無理じゃない？
Wait, isn't that impossible?
アクロバティックノエル
Acrobatic Noel
こより、右足が自由なんですよね
Koyori's right foot is free, actually
ノエルさん･･･ｗ
Noel-san... lol
さすがにもう無理か
As expected, it's impossible now
白銀ノエル OUT
Shirogane Noel OUT
博衣こより WIN
Hakui Koyori WIN
やりきったノエルさんの顔
Noel-san's face after giving it her all
こよちゃんもありがと～！
Koyo-chan, thank you too~!
こちらこそ～！
Likewise~!
楽しかったで～す！
It was fun!
この後も誕生日楽しんでくださ〜い！
Please continue to enjoy the birthday!
はい、続いては！ 違うお酒と新たなゲストが待っているので！
Yes, next! Different alcohol and new guests are waiting, so!
一旦、お口直しで録画済みのLIVEをご覧くださ〜い！
To cleanse your palate, please watch a pre-recorded LIVE performance~!
あー、恋の定義が分かんない
Ah, I don't know the definition of love
「好き」って気持ちが分かんない
I don't know the feeling of "liking" someone
要は恋してる時が恋らしい
In short, the time you're in love is love
客観的なエビデンスプリーズ
Objective evidence, please
あー、排他的論理理詰め
Ah, exclusive logical reasoning
解答不能の計算解けない
Can't solve this unsolvable calculation
要はそんな状態が怪しい
In short, that state is suspicious
アイノウ ユーノウ 待っててね
I know, you know, please wait
実証に愛を究を振って
Shake up love and investigation for demonstration
解を出して助けるのに
Even though I'm helping by providing the answer
間違ってて間違ってて
It's wrong, it's wrong
変えらんないこの気持ちは何だろう
What is this feeling that can't be changed?
検証イズメイド
Verification is made
ディスタンスモーションは相対性でステイ
Distance motion stays in relativity
チューリングラブ 見つめ合ったって解ない狙う
Turing Love, even if we gaze at each other, there's no answer, aiming for it
ワンルームラブ いま1 2 3で明かそうか
One room love, shall we reveal it now with 1, 2, 3?
どこまで生み出せちゃうかな
I wonder how much we can produce
あー 高鳴り出すアンサー
Ah, the answering pulse starts
重なったって確定せん 僕らのBPM
Even if overlapped, our BPM isn't fixed
チューリングラブ ちゅって待ったって信じないけど
Turing Love, even if I wait for a kiss, I won't believe it
フォーリンラブ いまはABCすらはべりそうだ
Falling Love, now even ABC seems to be fluttering
誰か教えてオイラー
Someone tell me, Euler
鼓動聴かせてフェルマー
Let me hear your heartbeat, Fermat
予測不能な精一杯 触れてみるさ
I'll try touching it with all my might, unpredictably
証明しよう
Let's prove it
間違いがないように証明しよう
Let's prove it so there are no mistakes
この感情全部全部証明しよう
Let's prove all of these feelings
正解があるなら証明しよう
If there's a correct answer, let's prove it
真実のチューリングラブ
True Turing Love
今日こそ証明したい 目に見えない
Today I want to prove it, the invisible...
無理難題を ASAP
Impossible task, ASAP
導き出したい たどり着きたい 最適解
Want to derive, want to reach, the optimal solution
何度空回ったって ぶつかっちゃったって
No matter how many times I spin my wheels or bump into things
不可思議なこのアノマリーを解き明かすは天才
The one to solve this mysterious anomaly is a genius
通常条件です
It's under normal conditions
3次元かっこ立体における2点AB間の距離を求めよ
Find the distance between two points A and B in 3D space
好きな感じだと思ってたのに
I thought it was a feeling I liked
座標も公式も見当たらないし
I can't find coordinates or a formula
資料にも載っていないから
Since it's not even in the data
君と見出してみてみたいじゃん
I want to try discovering it with you
三次元（かっこ）世界に負けるとも劣らぬ
Not inferior even to the 3D world
気持ちを求めた結果
The result of seeking these feelings
まるだって、バツだって
Whether it's a circle or a cross
不安にとって正解
It's the right answer for my anxiety
近くなって、遠くなって
Getting closer, getting further away
揺れるこの気持ちの針を
The needle of these swaying feelings...
条件付けステップエモーション
...is a conditioned step emotion
は正真正銘ミステイク
And a genuine mistake
チューリングラブ 曝け出した胸の痛くなるほど
Turing Love, to the point where my exposed chest hurts
証明は今も角度増しているような
The proof seems to be gaining more of an angle even now
曖昧文字返し 最大の仮説を
Returning ambiguous characters, the greatest hypothesis
今さあ、になら実証できそう
Now, it seems we can verify it
チューリングラブ 見つめあったら断ち切れないゼロ
Turing Love, when our eyes meet, we can't cut off the zero
ワンピーセズラブ 今ワンツースリーで明かそう
1/2 Love, now let's reveal it in one, two, three
どこまで生み出しちゃっちゃ ハート高鳴るアンサー
How far have we created? An answer that makes the heart pound
測ったって不確定性僕らのBPM
Even if measured, it's uncertain—our BPM
チューリングラブ 宙に舞ったってその因果も
Turing Love, even if dancing in the air, that causality too
フォーリンラブ 今はエクスタシーまでわかりそう
Fallin' Love, now it seems I understand even up to ecstasy
確かにそこで（ほら）
It's certainly there (Look)
確かにそこで（今）
It's certainly there (Now)
予測済み方程式 導いてみるさ
Let's try deriving the predicted equation
証明しよう 間違いないように
Let's prove it, so there's no mistake
証明しよう この感情全部全部
Let's prove it, all of these feelings
証明しよう 正解があるなら
Let's prove it, if there's a correct answer
証明しよう 定数さえ変えて
Let's prove it, even by changing the constants
証明しよう 間違いないように
Let's prove it, so there's no mistake
証明しよう この感情全部全部
Let's prove it, all of these feelings
証明しよう 正解があるなら
Let's prove it, if there's a correct answer
証明しよう シンプルな Q.E.D.
Let's prove it, a simple Q.E.D.
モザイクロール
Mozaik Role
作詞・作曲: DECO*27
Lyrics/Composition: DECO*27
とある事ばかり君に点き
Only certain things light up in you
捧げ尽くした力
The power I dedicated entirely
漏れ出す液を愛と形容してみた
I tried describing the leaking fluid as love
思い遣りの欠如と形だけの
Lack of consideration and just for show
媚びは腐れ縁の
The flattery of a bad relationship
君と私によく似ている
Resembles you and me well
それでも
Even so
好きとか
Like, or...
愛したっていいじゃないか
Isn't it fine if I love you?
縛り誰も触れないよう
Binding so no one else can touch
これも運命じゃないか
Isn't this fate too?
消える消える とある永久
Disappearing, disappearing, a certain eternity
終わる頃には君に飽きて
By the time it's over, I'll be tired of you
いるよ愛かよくか
I will; whether it's love or lust
解らず放つ言葉はなんとしよう
I don't know, so what should I call these words?
思い遣りの欠如と形だけの
Lack of consideration and just for show
媚びは腐れ縁の
The flattery of a bad relationship
君と私によく似ている
Resembles you and me well
それでも
Even so
いいから
It's fine
愛したって言うのですか
Are you saying that you loved me?
しがみ付いて藻掻くことを
Clinging on and struggling
殺したっていいじゃないか
Isn't it fine if you kill me?
君が嫌う私なんて
The 'me' that you hate
愛したっていいじゃないか
Isn't it fine if I love you?
縛り誰も触れないよう
Binding so no one else can touch
これも運命じゃないか
Isn't this fate too?
消える消える とある永久
Disappearing, disappearing, a certain eternity
はい、というわけでね
Alright, so then...
はい、はい！
Yes, yes!
続いてのゲストは…
The next guest is...
LIVEでもうわかったと思いますが！
I think you already know from the LIVE!
この方！
This person!
おー！
Ohhh!
お邪魔します！
Excuse me! / I'm joining you!
鷹嶺ルイ
Takane Lui
おめでとうございます！
Congratulations!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
ようこそ〜！
Welcome~!
酒臭えな、なんか
Man, it smells like alcohol here.
何飲んでたんですかぁ？
What were you guys drinking?
日本酒飲んでましたぁ～
We were drinking sake~
酔っ払ってます？大丈夫ですか？
Are you drunk? Are you okay?
いや、大丈夫、大丈夫！
No, I'm fine, I'm fine!
私、お邪魔して大丈夫ですか？
Is it okay for me to join?
大丈夫、大丈夫！
It's fine, it's fine!
…てことでね。ルイ姉といえば？
So... Speaking of Lui-nee?
私はワインが大好きです
I love wine!
おー、ワイン！
Oh, wine!
え、ワイン用意してくれてるんですか？
Eh, did you prepare wine for me?
そうなんです！
I did!
なに、ワイン飲めるの？
What, we get to drink wine?
最初のワインは、なにやら高貴なオーラを放っていますね。
The first wine seems to be emitting a noble aura.
貴腐ワイン、貴腐でございます
Kifu Wine, it's Noble Rot!
原料に貴腐菌(ボトリティス・シネレア)がついて育った葡萄を使用したワイン
A wine using grapes where a mold called Botrytis cinerea has attached and grown.
見えますか？
Can you see it?
貴腐葡萄
Noble rot grapes
なんて上品な…
How elegant...
貴腐菌がついた葡萄は干し山どうのようになり、糖分が凝縮される
When it attaches, water evaporates from the grape fruit, so the sugar content is concentrated.
おいしそ～!!
Looks delicious~!!
一般的な葡萄の糖度＝20～24度
貴腐葡萄の糖度＝60度を超える
While general grapes are 20 to 24 degrees,
some exceed 60 degrees.
甘口で有名ですね
It's famous for being sweet.
ワイン特有の香りとともに蜜のように甘美で芳醇な味わい
Along with the characteristic aroma of wine, it has a sweet and mellow taste like honey.
5万5000円
55,000 yen
おーゴーゴー
Oh, go go! / 55!
じゃあ私が注ぎましょうかね
Well then, I'll pour it.
かんぱーい!!
Cheers~!!
あうぅぅぅ～…!!
Auuu...!!
あまッ!!
So sweet!!
おいしい～!
むせ返るくらい甘い!!!
It's delicious~!
It's so sweet it makes me choke!!!
今まで飲んだワイン…
ワインで１番甘いかもしれない
The wines I've had until now...
This might be the sweetest wine ever.
アイスにかけて食べたい
I want to eat this over ice cream.
蜜みたいです本当に
It's really like honey.
カブトムシの気分
I feel like a beetle.
もう１本
One more bottle!
海底で造るやつ!!
The one made at the bottom of the sea!!
すごい有名なやつだ!!
That's a really famous one!!
深度60mの水圧と内部ガス圧を利用し熟成時のストレスをなくして造られたワイン
A wine made by utilizing water pressure at a 60m depth, eliminating stress during aging.
ガサガサしてるよ…
It feels rough...
あえて海に沈めるの？
They intentionally sink it in the sea?
「汚な〜」みたいな感じでね
...were like, "Dirty~".
これが味だよねぇ～w
This is the flavor, right~ lol
洗ったら？
Why not wash it?
3万3000円
33,000 yen
買えるかもしれないですね！
We might be able to buy it!
海の匂いがするような気がすふぅ
I feel like it smells like the sea...
しないだろ
No, it doesn't.
かんぱーい!!
Cheers~!!
意外と炭酸強い！
The carbonation is surprisingly strong!
シュワシュワしてる!!
It's fizzy!!
お酒感なくないですか？
Doesn't it feel like it's not alcohol?
全然違うよこれ!!
This is completely different!!
ちょっと辛口…？
A bit dry...?
皆さんなんか食べたかったりしませんか？
Does everyone want to eat something?
おつまみを用意しております！
I have snacks ready!
44ヶ月熟成 (ほぼ4年)
Aged for 44 months (almost 4 years)
約15万円
About 150,000 yen
生ハムの方が高いんですけど
The raw ham is more expensive!
（ワインより）生ハムの方が高いんですけど
Actually, the raw ham is more expensive than the wine.
ちょっと大きさを見て頂きたいｗ
I'd like you to see the size.
おおわぁぁあああ！！
Whoa!
でっけぇ!!
It's huge!!
バットやん
It's a bat.
鈍器やん
It's a blunt weapon.
10kgあるそうですよ
I heard it weighs 10kg.
10kg!?
じゃあちょっと頂きましょう 皆さんの元には
ちょっと切った物をお出ししております
Now then, let's eat. I've put out
some sliced pieces for all of you.
はい、ありがとうございます！
Yes, thank you!
私にも出して頂いてる！ありがた～い！
You gave some to me too! Thank you!
たべちゃうよぉ？いいですか？
I'm going to eat it. Is it okay?
食べちゃうよ！
I'll eat it!
すっごいしょっぱい...
It's really salty...
しょっぱい肉
Salty meat
しょっぱい しょっぱい肉
Salty, salty meat.
でもこれ 日本酒とも合うな これ
But this goes well with sake too.
嫌味のない塩辛さって感じ
It feels like a saltiness that isn't unpleasant.
あ、そう 嫌味のない塩
Ah, right. Salt that isn't unpleasant.
同じだね言ってること
You're saying the same thing.
一言一句いっしょｗ
Word for word the same.
何かすごい うわっ塩辛いっだけじゃなくて
It's not just "Wow, salty!", but...
丁寧な味がしますなんていうか
It has a refined taste, in a way.
凄くおしゃれなお店にある
Like in a very stylish shop...
粗塩みたいな味がする
It tastes like coarse salt.
岩塩みたいな
Like rock salt.
岩塩の その... それだけ舐めても全然味があるみたいな
Rock salt's... like you can taste it
even if you just lick that.
そうそうそうそう
Right, right, right, right.
外側の黄色い所は削いじゃうの？
Is the yellow part on the outside shaved off?
これ何か原木...
Is this a leg...?
削いじゃうみたいですよ！
It seems they shave it off!
中身だけ食べるみたいですけどね
Though it seems we only eat the inside.
シェフが頷いている
The chef is nodding.
骨になるまで削いでいくってこと？
Does it mean you keep shaving until it's just bone?
これさあらかじめ 生まれつきしょっぱいの？
Is this... salty by birth?
生まれつき？
By birth?
生ハムの原木に塩を...
Adding salt to the leg of ham...
塩食べさせるんじゃない!?
Aren't they feeding it salt!?
んなワケないよォ!!
No way!!
あ、違うの？そうじゃないの？
Oh, no? That wasn't it?
うちのなんかあの スタッフ...
No, our... staff...
それちょっとサイコパスすぎますね
That's a bit too psychopathic.
今すぐ何かを言いたそうな顔してる
He's making a face like he wants to
say something right now.
喧しい100万円飲み 最後の1品は高級品の代名詞、キャビア！
Yakamashi 1 Million Yen Drinking.
The final item is the synonym for luxury, caviar!
キャビア!!
Caviar!!
おお、入ってる！
Oh, it's in!
おいくらこれ？
How much is this?
高い！
Expensive!
キャビアです！素敵だ！
It's caviar! Amazing!
キャビアってどんな味がするの？
What does caviar taste like?
魚介やない？
Isn't it seafood?
卵やない？
Isn't it fish roe?
クラッカーと一緒に実食
Please try it with crackers.
キャビアの味なのか何なのかわかんないけど 今キャビアの味がするっ
I don't know if it's caviar flavor or what,
but right now it tastes like caviar!
たぶんそれがキャビアなんだわ
That's probably what caviar is.
これがキャビアだ！
This is caviar!
すごいコクがありますね このキャビア
It has a great richness, this caviar.
でもこれは 貴腐ワインと合いますね
But this goes well with noble rot wine.
100万円分 食べて頂きましたよ これで
With this, you've eaten 1 million yen worth.
おお～！おいしい！
Oh~! Delicious!
食べてるだけだよ？さっきから
We've just been eating, since a while ago.
このままで良いんか？
Is it okay like this?
どうかとは思いますけど ここでゲームをね
I have my doubts, but let's play a game here.
このまま帰っちゃいけないんだ
We can't just leave like this.
ですよ！まだ食べてるよ！
That's right! I'm still eating!
さっきゲームやったんだから ここでもゲームやりますよ
Since we played a game before,
we'll play one here too.
あ、ゲームあったんですね
Ah, there was a game.
そういう流れで行きましょうか じゃあ
Shall we go with that flow then?
椅子取りゲーム～！！
Musical Chairs~!!
やっできてしまいました この悪魔のようなゲーム
Yes, it's come. This devilish game.
悪魔なの？
Devilish?
なんで？
Why?
椅子取りゲームはいいですよ 分かりますよね？
Musical chairs is fine. You know it, right?
皆蹴落として頂いて 自分が座るという
曲が止まりましたら
Pushing everyone off and sitting down yourself
when the music stops.
ケツで押し出しOKですか？
Is pushing with butts OK?
まあまあまあ 紳士的にね
Well, well, gentlemanly.
100万円分のお酒を飲んだ皆さんですから
Since you all drank 1 million yen
worth of alcohol.
100万円の優雅な座りを ちゃんと見せて頂いて
You should show an elegant sitting
worthy of 1 million yen.
優雅にね
Elegantly.
ケツで押し出しはしない
No pushing with butts.
NGですよ それは
That's no good.
マリンさん勝っちゃうんでね
Because Marine-san would win.
手の押し出し お尻の押し出しダメですよ！
Pushing with hands or butts is not allowed!
ただ皆さんには 押し出されちゃった方は 1枚ずつ脱いで頂こうかなと
However, those who get pushed out will
have to take off one piece of clothing.
あら！
Oh!
誕生日の方からの希望ですけど
It's a request from the birthday person, but...
何ですか？
What is it?
ノエル先輩の キャストオフが見たいです
I want to see Noel-senpai's cast-off.
嵌めようぜー！！
Let's corner her~!!
椅子取りゲーム マジで強いからね
I'm really strong at musical chairs.
初耳情報
New information.
4人が敵だよ
All four are enemies.
急に悪質なゲームになりましたけど じゃあ行きますか？
It suddenly became a vicious game,
but shall we go?
それでは ミュージック スタート！
Then, music start!
(回転)どっち？
Which way (rotation)?
戌神ころね OUT!
Inugami Korone OUT!
えーちゃん!!
A-chan!!
審議入りますか？w
Shall we have a deliberation?
リプレイw
Replay.
どうなったんだ？
What happened?
私の横で座ってたころさんが なぜか椅子がなくなっていて
Koro-san, who was sitting next to me,
somehow lost her chair...
落ちてましたね 何か
She was falling, somehow.
ノエルちゃん嵌めようって言ってたじゃん
We said let's corner Noel-chan!
だって横にいたんだもんｗ
But she was right next to me.
座ってきたから
Because she sat down.
このケツでか～ｗ
This butt is so big~.
スポーツマンシップも何もないゲームでございますね
It's a game with no sportsmanship at all.
負けちゃったんで
Since you lost...
戌神ころね 一枚脱衣して頂きます
Inugami Korone, you'll have to take
off one piece of clothing.
ころちゃん
Koro-chan
着替えられましたか〜？
Were you able to change?
どうですか？
How is it?
はい…
Yes...
あ〜かわいい〜！
Ah, so cute!
あ、でもまだね、
Ah, but there's still,
チャックが残ってますから。
a zipper left.
え、なんか可愛いです。
Eh, it's kinda cute.
新鮮じゃないですか？
Isn't it fresh?
あれ、ころね、
Wait, Korone,
そんなにおっぱい大きかったかなあ…
was your chest always that big...?
やめなさい！！！
Stop that!!!
はい、こういう魔のゲームでございますので、
Yes, since it's this kind of diabolical game,
皆さん頑張って生き残ってください。
everyone please do your best to survive.
特にマリンさん危ないので。
Especially Marine-san, since she's in danger.
どゆこと？
What do you mean?
このさ、あ、こうなるのか。
This, ah, it goes like this.
ノエルとはね、公園でデートして
With Noel, I've even had a date in the park
ケツで押し出したこともあるから。
and pushed her off with my butt.
懐かしい。
How nostalgic.
はい、じゃあいきますよ。
Alright, here we go.
ミュージック、スタート！
Music, start!
あーっ！
Ah!
白銀ノエル OUT
Shirogane Noel OUT
やったやったやったー！
We did it, we did it!
白銀ノエル 一枚脱衣
Shirogane Noel: Taking off one layer
どうぞどうぞ。
Go ahead, go ahead.
すげー格好でいったけど、
She went in with a great pose,
途中で一回止まったの誰ですか？
but who stopped for a moment in the middle?
あらあら…
Oh my...
恥ずかしい…
How embarrassing...
ここボリって取るだけですよ。
You just take this off with a snap.
いやーこれちょっとラミィのチャンネルが危ぶまれる。
Gosh, Lamy's channel might be in danger because of this.
大丈夫だぞ。
It'll be fine.
どんとこい！
Bring it on!
3回戦いきましょう。
Let's go for Round 3.
露出度上がってきたなあ。
The exposure is increasing.
そうですね、ちょっと肌色が増えてきました。
That's true, there's a bit more skin showing now.
なんか歌ってるとね、止まってるのか聞こえなくて。
When we're singing, I can't hear if it's stopped.
一回無音にしてみよう！
Let's try it with no sound once!
オッケー、歌ってね。
Okay, sing along.
BGMを大きめに。
BGM loud.
スタート！
Start!
歌うんかいっ！
So you ARE singing!
あーっ！
Ah!
宝鐘マリン OUT
Houshou Marine OUT
すごい落ち方！
What a fall!
めちゃめちゃダサい落ち方したけど。
I fell in such an un-cool way.
果てしなくダサい落ち方
An endlessly un-cool fall
ラミィさんのチャンネルでダサい落ち方でしたね。
A very un-cool fall on Lamy-san's channel.
宝鐘マリン 一枚脱衣
Houshou Marine: Taking off one layer
ころねが次負けたら…
If Korone loses next...
ころねの恨みを感じた。
I felt Korone's grudge.
脱ぐしかないよ、もう。
I have no choice but to take it off now.
帰ってきましたか。
Are you back?
やだぁ〜！
Nooo!
さっきと一緒だよ。
It's the same as before.
何が恥ずかしいんじゃ。
What's there to be embarrassed about?
ここ入って。
Go in here.
怖いなあ。
This is scary.
それではいきますよ。
Alright, here we go.
ミュージック、スタート！
Music, start!
あーっ！
Ah!
雪花ラミィ OUT
Yukihana Lamy OUT
ラミィが隙間に座った。
Lamy sat in the gap.
可愛く座っちゃいましたけど。
She sat down quite cutely though.
雪花ラミィ 一枚脱衣
Yukihana Lamy: Taking off one layer
恥じらえよっ！
Have some modesty!
やっ、恥ずかしい…
Ah, how embarrassing...
茶番やな。
What a farce.
はい、これでみんな脱ぎ…あれ？
Yes, with this everyone has taken... wait?
ルイさん！！
Lui-san!!
脱げよ！
Take it off!
このまま空気を読まずに圧勝したい。
I want to win overwhelmingly without reading the room.
圧勝したいと思いまーす！
I intend to win overwhelmingly!
ミュージック、スタート！
Music, start!
あーっ！
Ah!
鷹嶺ルイ OUT
Takane Lui OUT
ものすごいイキってたのに。
You were acting so cocky.
圧勝死に様じゃねえか。
What a way to die after talking about victory.
悔しい、ガチで負けた…
How frustrating, I really lost...
REPLAY
鷹嶺ルイ 一枚脱衣
Lui Takane takes off one layer
脱げるかね？
Can she take it off?
来たかね？ 脱げたかね？
Did it come? Did she take it off?
恥ずかしい...
How embarrassing...
なんも変わってないじゃん
Nothing's changed
なんも露出してないだろ！
You're not showing anything!
それでは皆さん 心構えはいいですか？
Now everyone, are you ready?
はーい！
Yes!
いくぞ ミュージック スタート！
Here we go, music start!
先輩の圧に負けるな
Don't lose to your seniors' pressure!
可愛く 可愛く行きましょう
Let's go cutely, cutely!
誕生日ですからね
Because it's a birthday!
一、二、サーン！
One, two, three!
おらあっ！！
Take that!!
白銀ノエル OUT
Noel Shirogane OUT
ケツ圧に負けたんだけどい
I lost to the butt-pressure
今のはケツ圧やろ！！
That was definitely butt-pressure!!
いま実はマリン先輩 (椅子との)間に座ってました
Actually, Marine-senpai was sitting between the chairs
強すぎるでしょマリンさんやっぱり
Marine-san is too strong after all.
もしわしてこれって...
Wait, is this...
アウトですか？
Is it out?
宝鐘マリン OUT
Marine Houshou OUT
2アウトです
It's 2 out
あーノエルさっきは... 無理やり押し出したりしてごめんね？
Ah, Noel, sorry for pushing you out earlier?
団長もちょっと怒り過ぎちゃってごめんね
Danchou is also sorry for getting a bit too angry.
ふざけんなお前
Stop messing around!
雪花ラミィ生誕祭
Lamy Yukihana's Birthday Festival
一応誕生日ですからね 今回はね
It's my birthday, after all, this time.
ダメでしょケンカしたら！
No fighting allowed!
恥ずかしいよー
It's embarrassing~
仲直りのぎゅーして
Give a make-up hug
なんだこれ？
What's this?
てぇてぇな
So precious
てぇてぇか？今の
Was that precious? Just now.
よかったね 二人が負けて
Good thing the two of you lost.
エンディングとなりますね！
It's the ending then!
終わりなの！？
Is it over!?
リスナーさんはさ... みんなが水着になる事を望んでるんだ
The listeners... want everyone to be in swimsuits.
そうなんですか？
Is that so?
せんぱーい
Senpa~i
ねえノエル 二人きりになっちゃったね
Hey Noel, it's just the two of us now.
ラミィの部屋でさ こんな冬にさ 水着だなんて...
In Lamy's room, in winter, in swimsuits...
なんか友達の家でさ こうやってさ いかがわしい格好でさ...
In a friend's house, like this, in suspicious outfits...
やめてぇぇぇぇ！！
Stop it!!!!
ほらほらほら！
Hey, hey, hey!
恋な感じにんのやめて！！
Stop making it feel like romance!!
ラミィのお誕生日に来てくれてありがとー！！
Thank you for coming to Lamy's birthday!!
おめでとー！
Congratulations!
このあと グッズの告知あるのでよろしくお願いしますー！
There's an announcement for goods after this, so please look forward to it!
それではそれぞれ サービスショットを
Well then, everyone, a service shot.
ダメ！！ ダメぇぇ！！
No!! Nooo!!
はい 終わりです！！
Okay, that's it!!
バイバーイ！ お疲れ様でした！
Bye bye! Good job everyone!
ということで 雪花ラミィ誕生日記念2022 11月15日販売開始となっております
So, Lamy Yukihana Birthday Commemoration 2022, sales start on November 15th.
今回はですね 誕生日記念フルセットは 記念ボイス一種 記念グッズが三種となっております
This time, the birthday commemoration full set includes one type of commemorative voice and three types of commemorative goods.
まずは両面ブランケット 100万人記念の時の水族館の記念イラストなども担当してくださった Hong先生に描き下ろしていただきました
First, the double-sided blanket. It was drawn by Hong-sensei, who also did the aquarium commemorative illustration for the 1 million subscribers milestone.
しかもなんと フロントとバックで柄が違います
And surprisingly, the front and back have different designs.
好きな方を表にして使ってね
Use whichever side you like as the front.
そして今回のブランケット なんとサイズがちょっと大きめになっています
And this blanket is actually a bit larger in size.
横幅が140cm 縦が100cm
Width is 140cm, height is 100cm.
一人で使うのはもちろん 二人で一緒に被っても暖かくていいかもね
Of course it's good for one person, but it might be nice and warm for two people to use together too.
そして次は 3連結アクリルキーホルダー
Next is the 3-piece connected acrylic keychain.
みたらしねこ先生に描いていただきました
Drawn by Mitarashi Neko-sensei.
みんなが好きな順番に連結して使ってね
Connect them in any order you like.
そして公式についに出てきてしまいました やめなーダイカットクッション
And finally, it's officially here: the "Yamena-" die-cut cushion.
こちらフロントがノーマルやめな 裏がポルカ版のやめなになっています
The front is the normal Yamena, and the back is the Polka version of Yamena.
用途は色々 ふわふわしてる生地なので 枕にしたり 抱きしめたり クッションにしたり いろんな用途があるけれど...
It has many uses. Since it's fluffy fabric, you can use it as a pillow, hug it, use it as a cushion... there are many uses, but...
いじめるのはやめなー 可愛がってあげてください
Don't bully it. Please treat it kindly.
そして最後に シチュエーションボイス 「暖かい誕生日とその先へ」
And finally, the situation voice: "A Warm Birthday and Beyond".
こちらね 今回のグッズも含めたシチュエーションボイスになっているので
This is a situation voice that includes the goods from this time.
ぜひぜひブランケットとかね 用意して...
So please prepare the blanket and such...
…聴いてもらえると、とってもいいと思います。
...I think it'd be great if you could listen to it.
そして、フルセット購入特典は、
And for the full set purchase bonus,
HONG先生描き下ろしのポストカードに、
we have a postcard illustrated by HONG-sensei,
ラミィの複製サインとメッセージを入れて皆様にお届けいたします。
which includes my reproduced signature and message.
さらに、特典ボイス「誕生日前の出来事」。
Plus, there's a bonus voice titled 'Events Before My Birthday'.
これはですね、ちょっとラミィの
This one has some of
あまあまな独り言とかが色々入っておりまして、
my sweet mutterings and such,
あの、ま、これはですね、
Well, this is something
ぜひ絶対みんなに聴いてほしいなと。
I really want everyone to hear.
雪民さんにみんなに聴いてほしいなと思いますので、
I want all the Yukimin to hear it,
ぜひぜひフルセットをお迎えして、
so please do get the full set,
この特典ボイスを聴いてもらえると嬉しいです。
and I'd be happy if you'd listen to the bonus voice.
それではみんな、よろしくね。
Well then everyone, take care.
ありがとう！んーまっ！
Thank you! *Mwah!*
雪花ラミィ 2022 誕生日記念 11月15日販売開始
Yukihana Lamy Birthday Celebration 2022 On Sale November 15
今年も好き放題やります！やかまし娘晩酌100万円
Doing as we please again this year! Yakamashi Musume 1 Million Yen Dinner Party